University of Connecticut, Office of Institutional Research Records 1998.0288
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: An Inventory, 1950, 1960-2001; 37.0 Linear feet
  - Financial records, publications, 1950, 1960-1977, 1984-1996; 1.0 Linear feet Publications/reports in chronological order within subject (Box 1998.0288_26)
    Subjects include: American Council on Education, Educational Records: The Magazine of Higher Education, Financial Reports for the University of Connecticut.
  - Financial records, publications, 1977-1989, 1992-1995; 1.0 Linear feet Reports in chronological order by fiscal year (Box 1998.0288_27)
    Subjects include: Financial Reports for the University of Connecticut.
  - Administrative records, correspondence, notes, publications, 1967-1980; 1.0 Linear feet As received (Box 1998.0288_28)
    Subjects include: National Center for Higher Education Management Systems, National Science Foundation, University of Connecticut Office of Institutional Research Director Torrence.
  - Administrative records, publications, 1970-1987; 1.0 Linear feet As received (Box 1998.0288_29)
    Subjects include: Manpower Data Resource Service, Professional Women & Minorities, Scientific Engineering Technical Manpower Comments, Women's Issues.
  - Administrative records, correspondence, financial records, notes, publications, 1979, 1980s; 1.0 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs; binders (Box 1998.0288_30)
    Subjects include: Accreditation, Business, Engineering, Nursing, Pharmacy.
  - Administrative records, correspondence, notes, publications, 1970s; 1.0 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1998.0288_31)
    Subjects include: Accreditation, Business, Education, Engineering.
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1967, 1970s, 1980s, 1990s; 1.0 Linear feet As received (Box 1998.0288_32)
    Subjects include: New England State Universities Fact Books (University of Massachusetts, University of New Hampshire, University of Rhode Island, University of Vermont).
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1996-1997; 1.0 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs in alphabetical order (Box 1998.0288_33)
    Subjects include: Departmental annual reports and executive summaries from fiscal year 1997 (Academic Programs, Agriculture and Natural Resources, Agriculture (Ratcliffe Hicks School of), Allied Health, Animal Genetics, Animal Science, Avery Point Campus, Biotechnology Center, Business Administration, Computer Center, Cooperative Extension System, Education, Engineering, Extended and Continuing Education, Family Studies, Finance and Administration, Fine Arts, Hartford Campus, Honors Program, Instructional and Media Technology, International Affairs, Law, Liberal Arts and Sciences, Libraries, Marine Sciences and Technology Center, Materials Science, Mechanical Engineering, Museum of Art (William Benton), Natural Resources Management and Engineering, Nursing, Nutritional Sciences, Oral History, Pathobiology, Plant Science, Registrar, Research Foundation, Social Inquiry, Stamford Campus, Student Affairs, Technical Services, Torrington Campus, Waterbury Campus, Water Resources).
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1997-1998; 1.0 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs in alphabetical order (Box 1998.0288_34)
    Subjects include: Departmental annual reports and executive summaries from fiscal year 1998 (Academic Programs, African American Cultural Center, African American Studies, Agriculture and Natural Resources, Allied Health, Asian American Cultural Center, Avery Point Campus, Computer Center, Counseling Program for Intercollegiate Athletes, Education, Engineering, Extended and Continuing Education, Family Studies, Fine Arts, Graduate School, Hartford Campus, Honors Program, Instructional and Media Technology, Labor Education, Law, Liberal Arts and Sciences, Libraries, Marine Sciences, Materials Science, Nursing, Oral History, Pharmacy, Puerto Rican/Latin American Cultural Center, Registrar, Social Work, Stamford Campus, Technical Services, Waterbury Campus, Women's Center, Women's Studies).
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1998-1999; 1.0 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs in alphabetical order (Box 1998.0288_35)
    Subjects include: Departmental annual reports and executive summaries from fiscal year 1999 (Academic Programs, African American Cultural Center, Agriculture (Ratcliffe Hicks School of), Agriculture and Resource Economics, Allied Health, Animal Science, Anthropology, Art and Art History, Asian American Cultural Center, Asian American Studies, Avery Point Campus, Biotechnology Center, Business Administration, Chemical Engineering, Civil and Environmental Engineering, Communications and Information Technology, Computer Center, Computer Science and Engineering, Cooperative Extension System, Counseling Program for Intercollegiate Athletes, Education, Electrical and System Engineering, Engineering, Extended and Continuing Education, Family Studies, Fine Arts, Hartford Campus, Instructional and Media Technology, Labor Education, Law, Liberal Arts and Sciences, Libraries, Materials Science, Metallurgy and Materials Science Engineering, Modern and Classical Languages, Museum of Art (William Benton), Museum of Natural History (Connecticut State), Natural Resources Management and Engineering, Nursing, Nutrutional Sciences, Oral History, Pathobiology, Pharmacy, Plant Science, Puerto Rican/Latin American Cultural Center, Puerto Rican/Latin American Studies, Rainbow Center, Registrar, Sea Grant, Social Work, Stamford Campus, Technical Services, Torrington Campus, Transgenetic Animal Facility, Waterbury Campus, Women's Center, Women's Studies).
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1999-2000; 1.0 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs in alphabetical order (Box 1998.0288_36)
    Subjects include: Departmental annual reports and executive summaries from fiscal year 2000 (Academic Programs, Academic Renovations, Agriculture and Natural Resources, Agriculture (Ratcliffe Hicks School of), Allied Health, Animal Science, Anthropology, Art and Art History, Asian American Cultural Center, Avery Point Campus, Business Administration, Chemistry, Communication Sciences, Computer Center, Continuing Studies, Cooperative Extension Unit, Counseling Program for Intercollegiate Athletes, Dramatic Arts, Education, Economics, Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Engineering, English, Family Studies, Fine Arts, Geography, Geology and Geophysics, Hartford Campus, Health Fitness, History, Human Resources, Law, Liberal Arts and Sciences, Libraries, Linguistics, Marine Sciences, Marine Sciences and Technology Center, Materials Science, Mathematics, Modern and Classical Languages, Molecular and Cell Biology, Multicultural Affairs, Music, Natural Resources Management and Engineering, Nursing, Nutrutional Sciences, Oral History, Pathobiology, Pharmacy, Philosophy, Physics, Physiology and Neurobiology).
  - Administrative records, correspondence, publications, 1960-1989, 1993, 1999-2000; 1.0 Linear feet Some folders with labeled tabs; organized by subject (Box 1998.0288_37)
    Subjects include: Alumni Survey, Departmental annual reports and executive summaries from fiscal year 2000 (Plant Science, Political Science, Psychology, Puerto Rican/Latin American Cultural Center, Puerto Rican and Latino Studies Institute, Registrar, Sea Grant, Social Work, Sociology, Stamford Campus, Statistics, Technical Services, Torrington Campus, Transgenetic Animal Facility, Waterbury Campus, Women's Studies), Faculty Evaluation, Freshman Survey, Graduate degree enrollment, Provost's Ad Hoc Committee, Teaching Faculty Salaries and Demographic Characteristics, Transfers/branchfers and Storrs Natives, Undergraduate degree enrollment